A woman is giving conditions
before she gets into a
marriage
If the condition is lawful
If a condition
is not a condition
that makes halal, haram
or that makes haram,
halal
Then the man
accepts those conditions
The marriage is lawful
And it is lawful
For a man to accept that kind
of a marriage
There is a condition
This condition is not
changing halal
to haram
Neither is it changing haram
to halal
Then it is lawful
And it is very necessary
for the man to fulfill it
Because the prophet told us
about that
Alayhi Salatu Salam
From the strongest conditions
a man must
fulfill
must
are those
conditions by which
the women became lawful
for you to near them
So if at the beginning of the
Nikah you gave a
condition
Conditions are different from
promises
You can just promise,
we promise that
But it's a condition,
I will not marry you
unless you agree to these
things
These are different
They are stronger than just
promising
It's just like promising good
dealings
Promising this, promising
that
Promises are strong in the
Sharia
And from the ways of
Munafikun
Is that
When he promises
He fails the promise
So promises are strong too
But these
When they occur as shurut
They are stronger
As conditions for marriage,
they are stronger